人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：Iz    红豆包    奈奈良  Bazinga
校对：Iz          总监   IZ
时间轴：今        后期：吉吉
《开心汉堡店》
第三季第十七集
准备好  宝贝们
Open up, babies.
早饭时间到了
Time for breakfast.
谁想尝尝妈咪做的香肠
Who wants Mommy's sausage?
我不用了  谢谢
None for me, thanks.
连香肠都不吃了
No sausage?
怎么了  亲爱的
What's wrong, sweetie?
今天我要邀请小吉米作我的舞伴
Today's the day I'm going to ask Jimmy Jr. to the dance.
我不想一身的香肠味
I don't want sausage sweats.
为什么  我现在身上就有香肠味
Why? I'm wearing my sausage sweats right now.
我的宝贝要参加她在学校里的首场舞会了
Aw, my baby's going to her first school dance.
没什么大不了  我就没去过学校的舞会
It's not that big a deal. I never went to a school dance.
什么  你没去过学校的舞会
What? You never went to a school dance?
没有  我有别的事儿要忙呢
No, I had other things to do.
-比如说什么  老爸  -我学做皮具
- Like what, Dad? - Well, I did leather-tooling.
我做了一个腰带
I made a belt.
快换话题  快换话题
Somebody change the subject, somebody change the subject!
我无所谓的
Hey, I'm fine with it.
不是我错过了舞会
I didn't miss out on dances.
是他们错过了做皮具的机会
Those other kids missed out on leather.
鲍鲍
Aw, Bobby.
这就是我爱你的地方  你悲凉的人生
That's what I love about you: all your sad stories.
这不悲凉
It's not sad.
别说了  你吓到蒂娜了
Hush, you're scaring Tina.
在你约小吉米之前都别想这个
Put that out of your head before you ask Jimmy Jr.
要乐观  要乐观
Happy thoughts, happy thoughts.
皮带
Leather belts.
香肠
Sausage.
香肠皮带
Sausage belts.
好主意
That's a great idea.
-嗨  小吉米  -嘿  蒂娜
- Hi, Jimmy Jr. - Oh, hey, Tina.
你看到那两只在操场上打架的松鼠了吗
Did you see those two squirrels fighting in the courtyard?
说到舞会  你会去吗
Hey, speaking of the dance, are you planning on going?
你问我去不去跳舞
Am I going to the dance?
这样能算是回答了你的问题吗
Does this answer your question? Pyeah!
-这动作应该是在说"我去"  -没错
- Oh, that must be dancing for "Yes." - Yeah.
那么  你愿意当我的舞伴吗
Then, would you like to go to the dance with me?
我现在只能说  也许吧
Uh, the best I can do now is a maybe.
我想先看看我的行情
I want to know what all my options are first.
-有道理  -那是
- That makes sense. - Yeah, it does.
-何必现在就把自己套牢呢  -是的
- Because, why tie yourself down now? - Yeah.
你想知道都有哪些女生对你有兴趣
You know, you want to know all the girls that might be interested
-这样你就能权衡  -没错
- so you could weigh... - Right.
权衡比较一下
the pro... weigh them against each other.
好吧  回见
Okay, see you later.
好  再见
Okay, bye.
-蒂娜  -怎么了
- Tina. - Yeah?
这动作是什么意思
What's that dancing for?
你的裙子夹在内裤里了
Just... your skirt's stuck in your underwear.
多谢你告诉我
Oh, thanks for telling me.
-没事  整理下吧  -好
- All right, fix it. - Okay.
*我将永生*
*I'm gonna live forever*
*我将学会如何飞翔*
*I'm gonna learn how to fly...*
天哪
Oh, my God.
-蒂娜  -约书
- Tina? - Josh?
-你在这里干什么呢  -学校的任务
- What are you doing here? - I'm here for school.
这是我街头表演课的家庭作业
This is homework for my street performance class.
我上的是表演艺术中学
I go to the performing arts high school.
我跳芭蕾
I dance ballet.
坏男孩  酷
Oh, a bad boy. Cool.
这是谁
Who's this?
别告诉我她又是个舞迷
I hope she's not another Toe 'Ho.
-什么  -道格拉斯
- A what - Douglas.
舞蹈追星族  那些花痴  真让人伤神
A dance groupie. These hangers-on, they really sap your energy.
不  道格拉斯  这是蒂娜
No, Douglas, this is Tina.
我从没想过我还能再见到她
I never thought I'd see her again.
很好
Oh, great.
约书
Hey, hey, Josh.
我想做个一分钟的倒立动作来加分
I have to do a minute of handstands for extra credit.
你能帮我计时吗
Can you time me?
不行  我现在有事
No, I'm-I'm kind of busy right now.
那我只好自己计时了
I guess I'll just time myself, then.
一二三
One, two, three,
-四五六  -我后来再也没见过你
- four, five, six... - I haven't seen you since...
-道格拉斯  别这样好吗  -好吧
- Douglas, you got to stop, buddy, okay? - Okay.
非常抱歉  蒂娜  你刚才说到哪了
I'm so sorry, Tina. What were you saying?
我后来再也没见过你
I haven't seen you since...
自从我们上次接吻后
Since we kissed.
隔着鲜食超市的牛奶冰柜
On either side of the dairy case at Fresh Feed.
-那次很激烈  -也很冷
- It was hot. - And cold.
你为什么不给我打电话
Why didn't you call me?
不是  我记了你的号码
No, I wrote down your number,
但我把它放在跳舞的裤子里给汗水浸湿了
but I put it in my dance pants and it got all sweaty.
-跳舞的裤子  -是的
- Dance pants. - Yeah.
永远别把东西放跳舞的裤子里
Never put anything down dance pants.
我在想  我们学校周六有舞会
Hey, I was just thinking, our school dance is Saturday.
你愿意和我一起来吗
Will you come with me?
你难道不想先看看你的行情吗
Don't you want to know what your other options are?
不  小傻瓜  我想和你一起去
No, silly, I want to go with you.
我想去  但我们学校的舞会也是在周六
Well, that sounds fun, but my school dance is on Saturday, too,
今天我还约了一个没给我肯定答复的男生
and today I got a soft maybe from a boy I asked.
那么  我再通知你喽
So... I'll have to let you know?
非常公平  这是我的号码
That's totally fair. Here's my number.
哎呀  我把号码弄丢了
Oops, I lost it.
我知道你在开玩笑
I know you're kidding.
这就是我们之间的化学反应
Yep, that's our chemistry.
一定是
It sure is.
还是很酷的化学反应
Really cool chemistry, too.
道格拉斯  我求你了
Douglas, please!
我认得这种表情
Oh, I recognize that look.
有人要和小吉米去参加舞会了
Somebody's going to the dance with Jimmy Jr.
是的  也许会是我
Yes, and it might be me.
小吉米给了我一个"也许吧"的答复
Jimmy Jr. gave me a maybe.
好耶
All right!
我的"也许"小候选人
That's my little maybe baby.
你"也许"会成为舞会上最漂亮的女孩
You're gonna be the prettiest girl at the dance, maybe.
只是"也许"吗
Just a maybe?
他什么时候才能给你一个肯定的回复
When's he gonna give you a solid answer?
我希望他能快点
Soon, I hope.
因为约书也约我去参加他们学校的舞会
Because Josh asked me to go to his school dance, too.
太棒了
Well, that's great.
跟不把你当备胎的男孩去吧
Go with the kid who's not stringing you along.
记住  蒂娜  到手的呆瓜
Remember, Tina, a nerd in the hand is worth...
其实也什么价值  当我没说
not really that much, actually. Never mind.
肯定的答复肯定比"也许"强  亲爱的
A yes is better than a maybe, sweetie.
别到最后像你父亲一样
Don't end up like your father.
什么
Uh, what?
别到最后像你父亲一样
Don't end up like your father.
我想你说得对
I guess you're right.
但是  我已经花了3000个小时
But, I've logged over 3,000 fantasy hours
意淫我和小吉米的恋情了
on my relationship with Jimmy Jr.
不能说丢下就丢下
You don't just throw that away.
开心汉堡店  你好
Bob's Burgers. Hello?
我们可以吗
We can do it?
太好了  好激动
Yay. Oh, how exciting.
我们保证在我们的眼皮底下不会有人怀孕
No teens are gonna get pregnant on our watch.
周六见
I'll see you Saturday.
什么意思
Uh, what was all that?
准备摇摆起来吧  鲍鲍
Get ready to shake it, Bobby.
我们要去当蒂娜舞会的监护家长
We're gonna chaperone Tina's dance.
臭警察
Narc!
监护家长  这主意太烂了
Chaperone? That's a horrible idea.
老爸  这也是你的第一个舞会啊
Dad, your first dance.
我们可以一起准备了
We can get ready together.
是啊  你们可以给对方添点活力
Yeah, you can zip each other up.
嗨  小吉米
Hi, Jimmy Jr.
我想知道你是否已经决定了
I was wondering if you've decided
要和谁一起去参加舞会
who you're going to the dance with.
别见怪蒂娜  但你这样给我很大压力
Uh, no offense, Tina, but you're pressuring me right now,
男生不喜欢有压力
and guys don't like that.
那也许我该和别的约我的男生一起去
Well, then, maybe I'll go with the other boy who asked me.
什么  别的男生
Wha...? Another boy?
我刚决定了
Oh, uh... I just decided.
我和你一起去
I'll go with you.
等等  你决定和我一起去
Wait, you just decided you'll go with me
是因为你发现还有别的男生想约我
because you found out this other boy wants to?
和这个毫无关系
That has nothing to do with it.
-是谁  连尼吗  -不是
- Who is it? Lenny? - No.
他是挺帅  但还没帅到那种程度
I mean, he's good-looking, but he's not that good-looking.
况且  容颜是会凋谢的
Plus, looks fade.
不是连尼
It's not Lenny.
是内特吗
Was it Nate?
不是
No.
他有疱疹
'Cause he has herpes.
所以你是想和我一起去吗
So you're saying you want to go with me?
是的
Yes.
可约书也想和我去
And Josh wants to go with me.
选我吧  蒂娜
Choose me, Tina.
我邀请你在先
I asked you first.
但你先邀请的是我
But you asked me first.
我们有化学反应
We've got chemistry.
我有电臀
I've got a butt.
你看
Look at it.
我只邀请了你  你是唯一
I asked you and only you.
-别的你都不知道  -什么
- As far as you know. - What?
他刚才说  "别的你都不知道"
He said, "As far as you know."
没  我没说  是你说的
No, I didn't. You said it.
别管是谁说的
Don't worry about who said it.
看看这翘臀
Just watch the butt.
小吉米  我决定了
Jimmy Jr., I just decided.
舞会我要和...
I'm going to the dance with...
约书去
...Josh.
至少你还会改主意吧
Well, would you at least think about changing your mind?
用某位舞蹈帅哥的话来说  "也许吧"
As a handsome dancer once said, "Maybe."
那个舞蹈帅哥就是你
You're-you're the handsome dancer.
我知道  蒂娜
Yeah, I know, Tina.
小吉米曾经有搭上蒂娜这艘船的机会
Jimmy Jr. had a chance to hitch his trailer to the Tina truck,
但他错过了  如今这艘已驶向约书镇了
but now it's headed down the highway to Joshville.
嘟嘟
Honk, honk.
两个男孩同时喜欢蒂娜
Two boys like Tina at the same time?
俩人还都不是像罗伯特那样的纸人
And one of them's not even papier-mache, like Roberto was.
罗伯特怎么了
What happened to Roberto?
你跟他洗鸳鸯浴了吗
Did you try to shower with him?
是的
Yeah.
可以这么说吧
Maybe.
我为你高兴  蒂娜
Well, good for you, Tina.
等周六舞会我见着小吉米
When I see Jimmy Jr. at the dance on Saturday,
就跟他说
I'm gonna tell him,
"跳'时不再来舞'哭去吧  小子"
"Go do your 'you had your chance dance,' buddy."
等一下
Wait-wait a minute.
我们要为一个蒂娜不去的舞会做监护人吗
Now we're chaperoning a dance Tina's not even going to?
我们可不是为了她  鲍鲍
We're not doing it for her, Bobby.
是为了你啊
We're doing it for you.
我打心眼里希望  你们不是为了我
I really wish we weren't doing it for me.
醒醒吧  我们做什么都是为了你
Oh, wake up, we do everything for you.
老爸  只要相信自己  你就会蜕变的
Dad, if you believe you're beautiful, you will be.
我就这么过来的
I did.
不过你头发还有上升的空间
But maybe we can do something about that hair.
你洗头了吗
Did you wash it?
跟我们一起回家吧  蒂娜
Walk home with us, Tina.
你浑身散发着一种
There's just something about your smell
能让恶灵退散的气息
that keeps the mean dogs away.
今天不行
Not today.
约书要来接我
Josh is coming to pick me up.
紧身衣
Tights.
蒂娜  他当自己是超人啊
Tina, is he a superhero?
蒂娜
Hey, Tina.
约书
Hey, Josh.
我来接你了
So, I'm here to pick you up.
小心点
Whoa, careful!
明白没  我真的把你"接"起来了
Get it? I literally picked you up.
感觉就像被抱上了高脚凳  好浪漫
It was like being on a romantic stool.
这还只是冰山一角而已
Yeah, well, that was just a stool sample.
重头戏在后面呢
There's more where that came from.
十块钱赌你举不起吉恩
Ten bucks says you can't lift Gene.
把我弄到树上  然后跟大家说
Toss me into a tree, then tell everyone
我像正常小孩一样自己爬上去的
I climbed it myself like a normal boy.
等等  先举我  先举我
Wait, wait, wait. Pick me up, pick me up.
走你
Here we go.
放我下来  放我下来
Put me down! Put me down!
好  这就放你下来  放你下来了
Okay, now, now you're down! And now you're down.
感觉不赖
That was cool.
举女孩儿
Lifting a girl.
好了不起哦
Big deal.
抱歉  你是
I'm sorry. You are?
比你强的人
Better than you.
什么
And what?
他是小吉米
This is Jimmy Jr.,
另一个邀我去舞会的男生
the other boy who asked me to a dance.
这是约书  另一个邀我去舞会的男生
This is Josh, the other boy who asked me to a dance.
我是齐克
I'm Zeke.
我一个人去
I'm going stag.
就你还跳舞呢
So you dance, huh?
靠那两条小细腿吗
On those twigs?
不愧是小吉
You just got J-Ju-ed.
各位  有事慢慢说
Whoa, guys, slow down.
这点事用不着大动肝火的
Is this really worth it?
来吧  蒂娜
Come on, Tina.
我在冻酸奶店还预定了座位
We've got reservations at a frozen yogurt stand.
一看就是买不起普通酸奶的
Ha, can't afford regular yogurt.
真不敢相信蒂娜竟然有别的舞伴了
I can't believe Tina found another dancer.
还当着我的面  卿卿我我
She's rubbing that guy's feet in my face.
真是情敌相见  分外眼红啊
Somebody's as jealous as a bald guy in a mop factory.
我才不是眼红  齐克
I'm not jealous, Zeke.
我只是
I just don't!
不喜欢
Like!
那个男的
That guy!
冷静下
Calm down, now.
你想要她回来  那我们就追她回来
You want her back, we'll get her back.
你真这么想吗  齐克
You think so, Zeke?
我不知道  也许吧
I don't know, but maybe.
你刚刚说...
Well, you just said...
我有信心
Oh, just trust me!
有点儿信心
Kind of.
两个男的来追我  好难选
It's so hard when two boys want you.
你看起来很享受啊  蒂娜
You seem to be kind of enjoying all this attention, Tina.
别说了  鲍勃
Come on, Bob.
蒂娜等了这么些年才等到选择权到她手上
Tina had a long wait till she got to the buffet.
让她享受下怎么了
Let her pig out.
我的意思是  你不该拖着人家
I'm just saying, you shouldn't string boys along.
这是不对的
It's not right.
你不能像三十年前某人
You can't just tell a boy
在布坎南中学欺骗某个男孩那样
on the steps of Buchanan Middle School 30 years ago
明明答应了人家
that you're not going to the dance with him
最后却不跟人家跳舞
when you said you would.
怎么回事  鲍勃
What happened, Bob?
老爸  揭开那个伤疤
Yeah, Dad, open that wound.
给我们大家瞧瞧
Let's poke around in there.
好吧  好吧
All right, all right.
那年我13 岁 用零花钱买了朵饰花
I was 13, and I just spent my allowance on a corsage.
带女伴去舞会要先送她饰花
真蠢
Idiot.
你好  贝姬
Hey, Becky.
我给你买了饰花
I got you this corsage.
这饰花很配你的...
It goes really nice with your...
其他饰花
other corsage?
柯特送我的
Yeah, Curt gave it to me.
你好  柯特
Oh, hey, Curt.
你好
what's up?
对不起  我不知道怎么跟你说
Sorry, I didn't know how to tell you.
我想说这种方式可能最直接最容易
I thought this would be easiest.
是  是  确实很容易  贝姬
Yeah, yeah, this is, um... this is really easy, Becky.
谢谢
Thanks.
那好吧  里面见
Oh, well. I'll see you inside.
皮带不错
Great belt.
领结不错
Great neck.
你说什么
What'd you say?
没  没什么
Uh... nothing.
量你也不敢
Yeah, that's what I thought.
你裤链开了
Your fly's down.
没开
No, it isn't.
你骗到我了
Oh, got me.
对呀
Yep.
能不能只讲重点  老爸
Is this stuff really important to the story, Dad?
鲍鲍
Aw, Bobby.
这么着吧
That settles it.
我们来帮你弥补那个痛苦可怕的夜晚
We're gonna make up for that awful,
和你没跳成的舞  鲍鲍
terrible night and all your other missed dances, Bobby.
我讲这些不是图的这个  琳
That's not why I told the story, Lin.
这会是一场空前盛大
This is gonna be the biggest,
炫目无比的专为鲍鲍而办的学校舞会
glitziest, Bobby-est school dance ever.
如果要评监护王子  非你莫属
And if there's a chaperone king, it's gonna be you.
根本没有监护王子这种东西
There's no such thing as a chaperone king.
原先我们胡同里也没有浣熊王子来着
Well, there wasn't a raccoon king in our alley
直到后来我去选了一个我最喜欢的
until I went out there and picked my favorite one.
他的名字叫破坏小王爷
His name's Little King Trash Mouth.
他是同性恋
He's gay.
He's gay?
对的
Yeah.
怎么说
Why?
他有男朋友  两人刚结婚
He's got a boyfriend. They just got married.
咋了...
Wha...?
好了  小吉  把网准备好
All right, J-Ju, get your net ready.
我们要去钓蒂娜这条鳟鱼了
We're about to hook us a trout called Tina.
蒂娜
Hey, Tina.
小吉米
Hi, Jimmy Jr.
你好啊  美女
What's up, girl?
打倒你了  打倒你了
I got you! I got you!
放马过来吧
Come on!
不妙  小吉开始发威了
Uh-oh, J-Ju's starting to rally.
他打败我了
Oh, he beat me.
瞧瞧这小子
Oh, look at this boy.
瞧他浑身上下跃动的振振雄风
Look at that r-raging testosterone just throbbing out of him.
小妞  现在对他刮目相看了吧
How you like my boy now, lady?
我爆发了
Ah, I got mad.
我哥们儿可不是省油的灯
My main man's a crazy man.
我明白你的用意  小吉米
I know what you're doing, Jimmy Jr.
你是想把我夺回去做你的舞伴
You're trying to get me to go to the dance with you.
再接再厉吧
Well, try again.
我说真的  再接再厉
I mean it, try again.
现在吗
Um... right now?
不  过会儿
No, later.
不过别让齐克瞎掺合了
Just do something without Zeke.
要是这招行不通  那就没办法了
Well, if that didn't work, nothing will.
抱歉了  小吉
Sorry, J-Ju.
-咱们继续  -停手啊  齐克
- Now let's finish what we started! - No, Zeke!
你这小兔崽子
Ow! You little son of a bitch!
二位  蒂娜最近有提起过我吗
Hey, guys has, um... Tina been talking about me at all?
没啊
Um, no.
不走运啊  小吉  真心不走运
Tough break, Jr. Tough break.
你们能帮我夺回她芳心吗
Hey, will you guys help me get her back?
我们可以帮你  但要收费
We'll help you, for a price.
爱情可以用金钱来衡量吗
Can you really put a price on love?
当然可以  20美元
Yes, you can. It's $20.
好吧  告诉我该怎么做
Okay, just tell me what to do,
我一定照做  啥都行
and I'll do it. Anything.
不过要对蒂娜保密
Hey, but don't let Tina know.
拜托  小吉米
Jimmy Jr., please.
我们可是很专业很谨慎的
We are professional and discreet.
保证守口如瓶
We would never tell her.
蒂娜  小吉米刚刚雇我们把你抢回去
Hey, Tina, Jimmy Jr. just hired us to help win you back.
是吗
He did?
真是我听过最卑鄙无耻
That is the sleaziest, sneakiest,
浪漫美好的事了
most romantic thing I've ever heard.
好极了  我们能在网站上引用这句话吗
Great. Can we quote you on that for our Web site?
你能顺便帮我们做个网站吗
And could you make us a Web site?
挤兑约书行动出击
Operation Squash Josh is a go.
各就各位
Take your positions.
好啊  蒂娜
Hi, Tina.
哇  一匹马
Wow, a horse.
是我啦  小吉米
That's me, Jimmy Jr.
你在里面干嘛
What are you doing in there?
说"我爱你胜过干草"
Say, "I love you more than hay!"
说"我爱你  嘿"
Say, "I love you. Hey!"
我爱干草
I love hay.
挺好  因为你是只马嘛
Oh, that's nice. 'Cause you're a horse.
说"为爱甘心被俘"
Say, "Saddle up for love."
天上的卫星
Satellite above!
西雅图有毒品
Seattle has drugs.
原来毒品在那儿啊
Oh, that's where they have drugs.
进行得很顺利  情歌唱起来
It's going great! Hit her with the song.
开唱吧  小情种
Cue the tune, lover boy.
*T代表是你*
*"T" Is for the way*
歌词开头的字母连起来是蒂娜的名字
*让我无法呼吸*
*You take my breath away*
*I代表我喜欢*
*"I" Is for the way I like it*
*你让我无法呼吸*
*When you take my breath away*
*N代表没其它人能让我无法呼吸*
*"N" Is for no one else takes my breath away*
*A代表哮喘*
*And "A" Is for asthma*
*这种病让人们无法呼吸*
*That is a disease that takes people's breath away.*
-太棒了  -秒杀
- That was amazing. - Score.
-你成功了  -是啊  击掌庆贺
- You did it. - Yeah. High-five all around.
-势头不错  -蒂娜
- This is going good. - Hey, Tina.
-哪来的马  -小吉米扮成马
- What's with the horse? - Jimmy Jr. dressed up
给我个惊喜
like a horse to surprise me.
我知道蒂娜要什么
Yeah, I know what Tina wants.
顺便说一句
And, oh, by the way,
-我亲过她了  -我也亲了
- I kissed her. - I kissed her, too.
我亲她在先  你吻技很烂
Well, I kissed her first. And you kissed her worst.
你们的确都亲过我
Guys, you both have kissed me. It's true.
我也很感激你扮成这种
And I appreciate you dressing up
最不普通的普通动物来逗我
as the most magical non-magical animal there is.
不过我还是要去约书的舞会
But I want to go to Josh's dance.
-和约书一起  -正是在下
- With Josh. - That's me.
你越是拒绝我  我越想得到你
Ugh. When you tell me no, it makes me want you more!
不
Oh, no.
No.
不
你们不是知道怎么勾引你们姐姐吗
I thought you knew how to seduce your sister.
慢着  我们是在勾引我姐吗
Wait, that's what we're doing?
别急嘛
Be patient.
要想穿透那加厚镜片入她眼
Come on, it takes extra time
需要加倍的努力
to get through those extra thick glasses.
再说她正处在青春期  相当反复无常
Plus she's a teenager and they're so fickle.
我们干嘛要请个蠢保姆
Why do we have to get a stupid babysitter?
我怎么跟你说来着  注意用词
What did I say about using that word?
-你一点都不蠢  珍  -我知道
- You're not stupid, Jen. - I know.
我带了个小玩意儿让孩子们玩
I brought this puzzle for the kids to do.
瞧啊  是拧起来的钉子
Oh, look, it's nails all twisted up.
这未必一定解不开  但也很可能解不开
I'm not saying it's unsolvable, but it's probably unsolvable.
这个相当于钉子版的魔方
It's like the Rubik's Cube of nails.
是啊  看起来好神奇  珍
Yeah, that looks great, Jen.
解开了
Done!
-天哪  -你还有啥好玩的
- Oh, my God. - What else you got?
咱们可以看看我的手  其中一根手指
Uh... we could look at my hand. One of my fingers...
搅到吹叶机里去了
I got it caught in a leaf blower.
指关节就不长了
And so the knuckle didn't grow.
看这手啊
Oh, look at the hand.
真神奇
That's great.
谢谢
Thank you.
天哪  丑小鸭变天鹅了
Oh, my God, it's like a fairy tale!
好一对性感的豺狼虎豹
What a couple of sexy beasts!
咱们能出发了吗  你好  珍
Can we just go? Hi, Jen.
不行  我还要拍张照
Not before I get a picture, you can't.
你俩来  站一块儿
Come on, you two, get together.
说  浪漫
Say, "Romance."
-浪漫  -浪漫
- Romance. - Romance!
蒂娜  接你的车到了
Tina, your ride is here!
来瞧瞧  鲍鲍
And, uh... oh, what's this, Bobby?
我们的车也到了  看
Our ride is here, too! Look!
我跟豪车租赁处的人讲了你
I told the guy at the limo place
凄惨的故事  他给我们打了个折
your sad story, and he gave us a discount.
-我不想去了  -不行  你得去
- I'm staying home. - No, you're not.
来嘛  我还想站上天窗吼一嗓子呢
Come on, I want to stand up in the sun roof and yell bwah!
-好吗  -好吧
- Right? - Yup.
我有点小紧张
I'm a little nervous.
我明白  这里面高手如云
I know, there's a lot of talent in this room.
你们俩要记得拉伸韧带哦
Hey, remember to stretch, you two.
不然做这个动作的时候可能会拉伤
Or else you might get hurt doing this... Ha!
别担心  道格拉斯  我不会做那动作
Don't worry, Douglas. I won't be doing that.
我当然知道你不会啦  亲爱的
No, I know you won't, sweetheart.
我喜欢这曲子
I like this song.
我也是
So do I.
或许我们可以去舞池好好享受
Maybe we could like it on the dance floor.
把我想象成你的胡桃夹子
Just think of me as your Nutcracker.
抱歉  那是我唯一知道的芭蕾舞剧
Sorry, that's the only ballet I know.
嘴唇夹子怎么样
What about the lipcracker...?
芭蕾里真有这个吗  还是说你想接吻
Is that a real ballet, or are you asking me to kiss?
两者皆有
Both.
收回你们的狗嘴
Put the lips down!
小吉米
Jimmy Jr.?
蒂娜  我是来为你而战的
I came to fight for you, Tina.
-你说要打架吗  -不是
- Like fight-fight? - No.
我向你挑战  斗舞
I'm challenging you to a dance-off!
天哪  一场真正的斗舞
Oh, my God, a real dance-off!
我的主意  不谢
My idea. And you're welcome.
一场脱裤子秀吗  为了我
A pants off? For me?
Pants off Dance off美国Fuse电视台一档舞蹈秀节目 现形容激动人心的表演
不是  是斗舞秀
Uh, no, a dance-off.
那也差强人意吧
Oh. That's almost as good.
爸妈知道你们在这吗
Do Mom and Dad know you're here?
我不知道该跟他们整些啥
I didn't know what to do with them.
他们把迷也解了
They solved the puzzle.
我又没带备用的来
I didn't bring any backup puzzles.
我们盯着一根缺关节的手指
Yeah, we stared at a knuckle-less finger
看了有20来分钟
for about 20 minutes.
蒂娜  看着我
Uh, Tina, eyes on me.
-我要把你夺回来  -对哦  抱歉
- I'm winning you back. - Right, sorry.
《舞林争霸》节目组来电话了
So You Think You Can Dance called.
美国著名电视舞蹈真人秀节目
他们说你根本不会跳舞
They said, "You can't."
这笑话是你从学校里的
Did you, uh... learn that
"表演屁术"课学来的吗
joke at the School for Performing Farts?
真是我看过最棒的跟跳舞有关的对骂
These are the best insults about dancing I ever heard!
我不想下车
I don't ever want to leave this limo.
别这样嘛  小壁花
Oh, come on, you little wallflower.
wallflower 壁花  舞会中没有舞伴而坐着看的人
我会选你[摘你]的  我会摘你的花瓣
I'm gonna pick you. Gonna pluck your little petals.
好吧  我去
All right, I'm coming.
贝尔彻先生  贝尔彻女士
Mr. And Mrs. Belcher.
你们是穿得最隆重的舞会监护家长了
You are our best-dressed chaperones.
谢谢夸奖  雅各布森老师
Aw, thank you, Miss Jacobson.
这是我的鲍鲍第一次跳舞
It's my Bobby's first dance.
第一次以监护家长的身份跳舞
Uh, first dance as a chaperone.
我以前去过舞会
I've been to dances before.
那是当然  失陪一下  手给我放规矩
Of course. If you'll excuse me... Hands where I can see 'em!
雅各布森老师可是个美人呢  对吧
Ooh, Miss Jacobson's a looker, isn't she?
我也想说来着
You're telling me.
她怎么会是老师呢
Why is she a teacher?
她这级别都能在电视上演老师了
She should be, like, playing a teacher on TV.
好了  够了
All right. That's enough.
我只是觉得  我觉得  她
I'm just saying, I just... Yeah. She's, um...
-美得没天理  -我说够了
- ridiculously attractive. - Enough!
斗舞是小吉米提的  所以他先开始
Guys, Jimmy Jr. Called the dance-off, so he's gonna go first.
除了"禁忌舞步"不能跳  别的都可以
No moves are forbidden, except "The Forbidden Move"!
祝你们俩好运
Good luck to both of you.
这过程如果中你们大汗淋漓
And don't be self-conscious if you start sweating a lot,
T恤紧贴胸肌腹肌  也别感到难堪
and your shirt sticks to your chest and your abs.
-谢谢你  蒂娜  -谢谢你  蒂娜
- Thanks, Tina. - Thanks, Tina.
DJ  来点动感的音乐
DJ? Cue up something that rocks!
好耶
Yeah!
好了  我们跳过舞了  行了吧
Okay, there. We danced, all right?
我终于体验到我不曾有过的校舞会经历
I-I got the middle school dance experience I never had.
谢了  琳
Thank you, Lin.
就一支舞吗  鲍鲍  你根本脚都没动
One dance? Bobby, you didn't even move your feet.
你还是没融入气氛
You're still not getting into the spirit.
我们任务的  我们是舞会监护人啊
Look, we have a responsibility. We're chaperones.
我刚看见一个孩子舔另一个孩子的眼球了
I saw a kid lick another kid's eyeball.
我们是不是该惩罚下他们
Seems like something we should get him in trouble for.
等等  等等  鲍鲍
Wait, wait, wait, wait, Bobby.
生雅各布森老师的气是我不对
Uh, I'm sorry I blew my lid about Miss Jacobson.
没关系的
It's fine.
我只是觉得  她  她真的是个可人儿
It's just, you know, she-she really is a hottie.
我敢说要是她邀请  你会再跳一支的
I bet if she asked you to dance, you'd take another spin.
对吧  对吧
Wouldn't you? Wouldn't you?
不  不  我  不  我没兴趣
No. No. I... No. I would not be interested.
你就承认吧
Go on, say it.
承认你更想和她跳舞
Say you'd rather dance with her!
-我我  啥  我  -承认吧
- I-I... Wh... I... - Say it!
这是送给你的  接好了
This is for you! There!
琳达  啥意思
Linda. What the hell?
腾云驾雾  腾云驾雾
Cut the fog, man! Cut the fog!
漂亮
Yeah!
道格拉斯  你怎么看
Douglas, what do you think?
我是慢慢来呢还是直接上猛的
Take it slow or go rough?
约书  有多猛来多猛
Josh, you be as nasty as you need to be.
对  来猛的
Yes, nasty.
DJ  放我的音乐
DJ, my music.
看着就像只对着天空乱抓一气的狮子
Wow, he looks like a lion murdering a cloud.
我懂  太美了
I know. Isn't it beautiful?
琳达  你怎么了
Linda? What's wrong with you?
你在里面干嘛呢
What are you doing in there?
我们就  我在跟我闺蜜说话呢
We just... I'm talking to my girlfriends!
走开  鲍勃
Go away, Bob!
你不是想和雅各布森老师跳舞么
You want to dance with Miss Jacobson!
你不是觉得她比我好看么
You think she's prettier than me.
她是很漂亮  但那不重要  谁在乎呢
Yes, she's hot, but it doesn't matter. Who cares?
我  我现在就回舞池去
Look, I-I'm going to go back out to the dance
装作什么也没发生
and pretend none of this is happening
你就别像个中学生一样闹脾气了  琳达
because you're acting like a middle schooler, Linda,
-我  -骗到你啦
- and I am, uh... Oh... - Gotcha!
-所以这都是你  -可以发挥发挥嘛
- So that was just so... - So you could have a little drama.
这不是你的中学舞会吗
It's your middle school dance.
如何  是不是觉得蛮有意思
What, did you think these things are fun? Come on.
你绝对是疯了
You are definitely nuts.
现你在更能融入气氛了吧
But now you're more in the spirit, right?
是不是可以再跳几支
You got some more dance in your pants, don't you?
-来嘛  -我不知道  我不知道
- Ooh. Come on. - I don't. No. That... I don't know.
-别这样  -这东西或许有用
- Stop. - Come on, this might help right here.
我带了杜松子酒
I brought some schnapps.
在这儿吗  我们会有麻烦的  琳
Here? We'll get in trouble, Lin.
这就对了
That's right.
不对  这很不对
That's bad. That is really bad.
我的天  感觉来了
Oh, my Go... oh, my God, it just got good.
-看吧  -你还带了两瓶
- Look. - You brought two?
两瓶一起来  一起来
Double-fist it. Double-fist it.
人家不想把桃子味的和薄荷味的混在一起
I'm not mixing peach and mint.
于是这只天鹅终于骄傲地  死去了
And with great dignity, the swan... dies.
我该带玫瑰花来扔的
Why did I not bring any roses to toss?
我怎么就没随身带玫瑰呢
I should always carry roses!
这还没完
This isn't over!
互飙舞技环节
Lightning round!
DJ  开始吧
DJ, kick it!
我在这  我不在  我在这  我不在
Here I am. No, I'm not. Here I am. No, I'm not.
我在这  我不在
Here I am. No, I'm not.
我跳
Jump.
住手  关掉音乐  有人会受伤的
Stop. Turn off the music. Someone's gonna get hurt.
我没法选
I can't choose.
也许我不用选
Maybe I don't have to choose.
我们可以的  可以制定一个情人值日表
We can make this work. We'll come up with a make-out wheel.
就像家务值班表一样
Kind of like a chore wheel.
-我不想这样  -我也是
- Uh, I don't want to do this. - Yeah, me, neither.
试试嘛  给三角恋一次机会
Give it a chance. Let's put the "Try" In "Triangle."
不了  谢谢  再联系吧
Um, no, thanks. Talk to you later, okay?
我今晚很开心  除了这个结尾
Tonight was really fun. Until all of this.
结尾就是一团糟
This was a mess.
我都有点忘记我本来是来这儿干嘛了
Yeah, um, I kind of forgot what I was even doing here.
虽然打成了平局  但也诞生了输家
Well, we have a draw, but we also have a loser.
这个输家当然就是  你  蒂娜
Which would, of course, be you, Tina.
等你不再想鱼和熊掌兼得的时候
If you ever go back to being a one-boy girl,
再来找我吧
you know where to find me. And, hey,
小吉米  你跳得不错
Jimmy Jr., you got some great moves.
你跟我想到一块儿去了吗
You thinking what I'm thinking?
来吧
Let's do this.
美女  就剩我俩了
Oh, yeah, girl! We got ourselves a dance on!
-真可惜  小蒂  -我太贪心了
- Too bad, T. - I got greedy and grabby.
但有两个男生曾经争着要我呢
But I had two boys fighting over me.
我已经满足了
I'm thankful for that.
真可惜你没能把小吉米和约书
Sorry you weren't able to make Jimmy Jr. And Josh
变成你的家政工
your sister-wives.
也许下一只舞还有机会
Hey, maybe next dance.
你手离屁股太近了
You flew too close to the buns.
注意你们的手哦
Watch the hands.
贝尔彻先生  贝尔彻夫人
Um, Mr. And Mrs. Belcher? Hi.
我希望你们能低调点
I'm gonna have to ask you to tone it down a little bit.
你是说像这样吗
Oh, you mean tone it down like this? Whoop!
不  我不是这个意思
No. That is not what I mean.
这是完全不符合规定的行为
This is completely inappropriate behavior.
鲍鲍的第一支舞
Bobby's first dance!
-天哪  琳  -杜松子酒都吐出来了
- Oh, my God. Oh, Lin. - Oh, the schnapps.
-琳  -还有桃子的味道
- Oh, Lin. - Oh, it tastes like peach.
弄得我一身都是了
Oh, man. That's all over me.
我得把衣服脱了  我要
Ah, I got to take my shirt off. I'm gonna...
-我也要吐了  -谁来帮下忙
- I'm gonna lose it, too! - Can I get a little help over here?
-我不行了  -这两个  给我拖出去
- I'm gonna lose it! - All right, these two, out. Right here.
你生气的时候更漂亮了呢  小美女
Ooh, you're even prettier when you're angry, little lady.
我没事  我没事
I got it! I got it!
你们又不是保安  你们是蒂娜的朋友
You're not security. You're friends with Tina.
-把手拿开  -干什么  喂
- Hey. Get your hands off me. - What? Hey!
-给我弄出去  -把手拿开  小兄弟
- These two. Get 'em out. - Get your hands off me, little guy.
*T代表你让我无法呼吸*
*"T" Is for the way you take my breath away *
*I代表我喜欢你让我无法呼吸*
*"I" Is for the way I like it when you take my breath away*
*N代表没其它人能让我无法呼吸*
*"N" Is for no one else takes my breath away*
*A代表哮喘*
*And "A" Is for asthma that is a disease*
*这种病让人们无法呼吸*
*That takes people's breath away!*
挺好  因为你是只马嘛
Oh, that's nice. 'Cause you're a horse.